11degrees.co.uk 2019-05-30

# 11 Degrees Clothing | Privacy Policy

By submitting your information through your use of this website, you consent to the use of that information by 11 Degrees as set out below.

 **Introduction**

For the purposes of  Data Protection the Data Controller for this website is 11 Degrees Trading Ltd ("11 Degrees"). The privacy and security of our customers is important to us. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information, and the procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

 **The information we collect and how we use it**

If you wish to register for our email service you must provide us with your name and email address. From time to time we may provide the information that you have provided in subscribing to the email service or in purchasing services through the website to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the services we provide.

We may wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other services, products or information from 11 degrees that we think may be of interest to you. We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an email message to admin@11degrees.co.uk  
We would like to provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, please send an email message to admin@11degrees.co.uk  
All historic data remains for analysis.  
Alternatively, please see paragraph 6 below for information on other methods for updating your preferences.

Aside from the matters laid out above, your personal data will not be disclosed to any third party save with your consent or as required by a regulatory body or under a court order. 

 **Our use of cookies and other information gathering technologies**

11 Degrees employs information gathering technologies for the purposes of collecting information and statistics about the users of this site, but such information will not be used to identify any individual. The purpose of gathering such information is to assist us to analyse the use of the website and revise it for the benefit of our clients by making your visit to the site more efficient and to improve and increase the content found to be most popular.

We also employ cookies on this site. Cookies are small text files used on the internet for a variety of purposes. We use cookies to make your use of the website more efficient, for example by saving you the trouble of re-entering information. Although the cookie may provide an automated identification of your computer, no personal data is stored in the cookie.

You may adjust your computer's settings so as to block cookies, to accept or reject cookies from specific websites, or to accept them only on?confirmation?from you. Because of the wide variety of browsers and operating systems used by our customers we cannot provide detailed instructions for this, however your browser should contain details in its help facility. You should be aware that if you choose to block cookies, the site may not work as efficiently as intended. Please see our cookie policy [HERE](http://www.11degrees.co.uk/cookies "cookie link")

 **How we protect your information**

The internet is not a secure medium. We have put in place various security measures but you are advised to treat the internet as an insecure medium in all your communications with us. However, payments made through this website are handled using secure socket layer technology or other technology which is at least (if not more) secure than that.

Your payment information will not be disclosed to anyone under any circumstances other than as necessary for the sale concerned and will not be retained by us thereafter.

 **Sale of business**

If 11 Degrees or the business operated through this website is integrated into any other company or organisation your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective operators and their advisers and will be passed on to the new operators of 11 Degrees or the business operated through this website.

 **Updating your details**

If any of the personal information that you have provided to 11 Degrees changes, for example if you change your email address, please advise us by sending an email to admin@11degrees.co.uk.

 **Marketing Messages**

If you have said we can, we’ll send you marketing messages by email and/or sms to keep you informed about new products, latest news and special offers

How to stop marketing messages from 11 Degrees

You can unsubscribe from marketing messages from us at any time.

• If you have an account with us you can go to ‘my account’ and unsubscribe

• By clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any marketing email

• By contacting our Customer service team on admin@11degrees.co.uk

Once you do this, we will update your profile to ensure that you don’t receive further marketing messages - please note it might take up to 72 hours to update our systems, so you may still receive marketing messages whilst your request is being processed. Stopping marketing messages will not stop email communications for necessary service messages eg. order updates

 **Your consent**

By submitting the information referred to above, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We may also email you should you make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the website will signify that you agree to any such changes.

Owing to the global nature of the internet's infrastructure the information you provide may be temporarily transferred to and stored in countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy whilst in transmission.  
Occasionally it is necessary for us to change this Privacy Policy, so please remember to check back from time to time.

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact us at admin@11degrees.co.uk

 **11 Degrees Limited is registered in England No:  08829279 and has its registered office at Kendal House, Murley Moss Business Park, Oxenholme Road, Kendal, Cumbria, England, LA9 7RL**
